<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Devfest Norway 2020</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Devfest Norway 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Famous App UIs Broken Down in Flutter Widgets</title><link>/sessions/famous_app_uis_in_flutter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/sessions/famous_app_uis_in_flutter/</guid><description>User Interfaces of famous Mobile Apps will be deconstructed to the basic Flutter widgets, which, when put together, can replicate those very UIs in Flutter! This session will equip Flutter Developers with critical UI observation skills to drive insights required to build a stellar UI in Flutter, and that too, in minimum time.
In this Talk, I’ll go over the User Interfaces of 2-3 most famous Mobile Apps. I’ll handpick some of the core screens of these apps, explaining my observation on the UI elements for each of them, and then deconstructing each of those elements to their equivalent Flutter widgets and their collective placements and styling.</description></item><item><title>Tales of a Mobile DevOps</title><link>/sessions/mobile_devops/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/sessions/mobile_devops/</guid><description>There is a lot of material on developing mobile apps, but how about shipping it to the real world? In this session we will go through what is the role of a Mobile Infrastructure team and why is crucial to let your app reach your end users.
If you&amp;rsquo;re developing mobile apps, you probably know what&amp;rsquo;s one of your most important KPI: Store Rating.
In such an environment, speed is key.</description></item><item><title>Want more from your frontend framework! Re-thinking web dev experience</title><link>/sessions/want_more_from_your_frontend/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/sessions/want_more_from_your_frontend/</guid><description>Do you also love creating useful (web)apps and get easily frustrated by any friction in the development process? I will compare Redux + REST with a full-stack, component-centric solution based on a graph API (think GraphQL) that I came to love. You might not be able to use the same framework - Fulcro - but you can still look for similar, more developer-friendly solutions that implement some of the same ideas and provide some of the same functionality.</description></item><item><title>Get ready for Devfest Norway 2020!</title><link>/blog/get-ready-for-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/get-ready-for-2020/</guid><description>#devfestno 2020 goes online and will be free! 😍👏
We are very excited and happy about this decision!
Stay tuned! 🚀
What&amp;rsquo;s next? Get your free ticket to receive a link to the stream before the event start. We will post all updates on our Twitter @devfestno, stay tuned!</description></item><item><title/><link>/speakers/gaute_meek_olsen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/gaute_meek_olsen/</guid><description>Gaute is a software developer from Norway. He always likes to learn new technology and create hobby projects from what he has learned. He mostly programmes in JavaScript, C#, Java and Kotlin.
Website Twitter GitHub</description></item><item><title/><link>/speakers/nivetha_maran/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/nivetha_maran/</guid><description>I am a Software Engineer with focus on frontend technologies on Angular, React, Javascript, etc, with industry experience of around 3 years. Besides my regular job, I am an ambassador for GDG/WTM Chennai community. More info can be found here https://gdg.community.dev/gdg-chennai/, where we conduct technical meetups, conferences, workshops to develop tech and soft skills for the local developer community. And a PROUD feminist.
Twitter</description></item><item><title>A Multiplatform triathlon -- Kotlin through Android, iOS and web</title><link>/sessions/multiplatform_triatholin_in_kotlin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/multiplatform_triatholin_in_kotlin/</guid><description>Do you ever had the dream that you could develop for one platform and you could easily reuse the code and create an app on another platform? Yup, there&amp;rsquo;s Kotlin Multiplatform 🙌
For several years now, we’ve been trying to find new solutions on how we could develop a single project and run it on all platforms. We’ve been seeing all types of solutions: some are web-based, others require you to learn a new language, and others even may require that you pay a monthly fee to use.</description></item><item><title>A Multiplatform triathlon -- Kotlin through Android, iOS and web</title><link>/speakers/carlos_mota/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/carlos_mota/</guid><description>Android tech lead at WIT Software, he can easily be spotted there working on the company RCS solution. Carlos is enthusiastic for new technology and always trying to reach those last 20% of all of his side projects that seem to be really far away. He loves to share his knowledge with others either by giving talks, teaching, writing or getting a cold beer in the nearest pub.
GDG Coimbra organizer and Kotlin evangelist, he also has a huge passion for travel, photography, space and the occasional run.</description></item><item><title>Angular Material Design</title><link>/sessions/angular_material_design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/angular_material_design/</guid><description>You may have heard of @angular/material, or added few in your project - but how can developers take advantage of Material to create cohesive applications? In this talk, we’ll learn how to leverage Angular and Material Design to create standard theming, custom design systems, and explore what’s next in Angular Material Design.
I will be covering @angular/material and Material Design within Angular. Since these are both Google products, the Google team has a unique vantage of understanding how we can better leverage Material Design within our applications moving forwards.</description></item><item><title>Angular Material Design</title><link>/speakers/emma_twersky/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/emma_twersky/</guid><description>Emma is a Developer Advocate at Google. She is passionate about good user experiences and design.
I am new to the Google Angular team, and previously spoke about Android and accessibility. I am scheduled to speak at Dutch Angular, several other meetups, GDG UK + Ireland and ngChina in the upcoming month.
Twitter</description></item><item><title>Beyond ES6 - New things in JavaScript</title><link>/sessions/beyond_es6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/beyond_es6/</guid><description>From 2015, when ES6 was introduced, JavaScript has added new features to the language each year. ES6 is considered modern JavaScript, but that is now 5 years ago. What has happened in the last 5 years? Let me show you what&amp;rsquo;s new in JavaScript.
I will show code and explain how the new features from the last 5 releases can help us.
ES7/ES2016: includes, exponentiation
ES8/ES2017: async &amp;amp; await, String padding, Object values &amp;amp; entries</description></item><item><title>CI/CD for Serverless Applications on CloudRun</title><link>/sessions/serverless_on_cloudrun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/serverless_on_cloudrun/</guid><description>This is a hands-on demo of building a CI/CD pipeline for a web application deployed as a Serverless app using CloudRun.
Serverless application deployment is becoming quite popular and when it comes to GCP - CloudRun is the goto product/solution. This talk describes deploying a web application on CloudRun and how you can integrate your build pipelines using Cloud Build for the same. The talk would cover an end-to-end demo from building a docker container, pushing to GCR and then linking your repository to CloudBuild and ultimately deploying to CloudRun.</description></item><item><title>CI/CD for Serverless Applications on CloudRun</title><link>/speakers/dharmesh_vaya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/dharmesh_vaya/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Google Developer Expert (GDE) who works as a developer evangelist at Auth0. At Auth0 we&amp;rsquo;re trying to make authentication and identification as easy as possible, while still keeping it secure.
After office hours, I like to play around with the web-audio API, and other &amp;ldquo;exotic&amp;rdquo; browser API&amp;rsquo;s. One of my side projects is a library to add audio effects to an audio input using JavaScript.
Twitter</description></item><item><title>Closing words</title><link>/sessions/__close/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/__close/</guid><description>Closing words of the day</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>Our statement This &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t be a jerk&amp;rdquo; policy is a shortened, more casual version of the longer Code of Conduct policy. Read full version.
DevfestNorway Team prides itself on being an open, respectful, and inclusive community. That means jerky behavior isn’t allowed at DevfestNorway meetings. Because we know that it’s not obvious to everyone, here’s a reminder of the things we don’t allow: jokes or offensive comments about sex/sexuality/race/religion/nationality/body size, showing porn in public, touching people uninvited, or continuing to interact with someone after they’ve asked you to stop.</description></item><item><title>Designing Fair Machine Learning Models</title><link>/sessions/fair_ml_models/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/fair_ml_models/</guid><description>The talk illustrates different aspects of building fair models. It further exemplifies with different use-cases as to how different ML models (traditional and deep learning) can be built using different constraints and how we can choose the right KPI metrics to evaluate its fairness.
This talk will be co-presented with fellow ML GDE Charmi Chokshi.</description></item><item><title>Designing Fair Machine Learning Models</title><link>/speakers/charmi_chokshi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/charmi_chokshi/</guid><description>Playing with data and predicting possibilities based on it is Charmi&amp;rsquo;s passion! From giving tech sessions at the local meetups to delivering tech-talks at global stages, she loves helping developers &amp;amp; students who look forward to growing their careers in the field of Artificial Intelligence.
She has worked in the pipeline of the Smart-cities Mission of India in the Deep Learning and Computer Vision domain at the Indian Space Research Organisation.</description></item><item><title>Designing Fair Machine Learning Models</title><link>/speakers/sharmistha_chatterjee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/sharmistha_chatterjee/</guid><description>Sharmistha Chatterjee is a Data Science Evangelist with vast professional experience in the field of Machine Learning and Cloud applications. She has graduated from Aalto University (formerly Helsinki University of Technology). She has proven experience in both doing AI research and implementing scalable AI solutions for enterprises. She tries to bridge the gap between theory and practice.
She is an active blogger, speaker at different AI/ML conferences, Google Developer Expert in Machine Learning, and a Professional Cloud Architect.</description></item><item><title>Directives in Angular</title><link>/sessions/directives_in_angular/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/directives_in_angular/</guid><description>I will be talking about the types of directives that are available in Angular and the usecases for the same.</description></item><item><title>Famous App UIs Broken Down in Flutter Widgets</title><link>/speakers/sakina_abbas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/sakina_abbas/</guid><description>Being the Cofounder and CEO of ReacTree, a new-gen Software Development house, Sakina Abbas is all about solving problems through technology. She started off as a native Android developer and is now leading Flutter development and DevOps at ReacTree. To date, she has provided consultancies to numerous international and local clients and has built a number of custom solutions.
Website Twitter</description></item><item><title>FAQs</title><link>/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/faq/</guid><description>General What is Devfest Norway? The DevFest, or ‘Developers Festival’, is a technical conference for developers. It is aimed at students, professionals or simply curious technophiles.
Organizing communities GDG Oslo GDG cloud Oslo GDG Bergen GDG Trondheim GDG Sørlandet GDG Stavanger</description></item><item><title>GDG Bergen</title><link>/partners/communities/gdg_bergen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/communities/gdg_bergen/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Bergen</title><link>/partners/organizers/gdg_bergen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/organizers/gdg_bergen/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Cloud Olso</title><link>/partners/communities/gdg_cloud_oslo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/communities/gdg_cloud_oslo/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Cloud Oslo, Norway</title><link>/partners/organizers/gdg_cloud_oslo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/organizers/gdg_cloud_oslo/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Oslo</title><link>/partners/communities/gdg_oslo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/communities/gdg_oslo/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Oslo</title><link>/partners/organizers/gdg_oslo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/organizers/gdg_oslo/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Stavanger</title><link>/partners/communities/gdg_stavanger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/communities/gdg_stavanger/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Stavanger</title><link>/partners/organizers/gdg_stavanger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/organizers/gdg_stavanger/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Sørlandet</title><link>/partners/communities/gdg_sorlandet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/communities/gdg_sorlandet/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Sørlandet</title><link>/partners/organizers/gdg_sorlandet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/organizers/gdg_sorlandet/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Trondheim</title><link>/partners/communities/gdg_trondheim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/communities/gdg_trondheim/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GDG Trondheim</title><link>/partners/organizers/gdg_trondheim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/organizers/gdg_trondheim/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Google</title><link>/partners/sponsors/google/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/partners/sponsors/google/</guid><description>Google is the worldwide leader in software, services, devices and solutions that help people and businesses realize their full potential.</description></item><item><title>Help! My Memory is Leaking</title><link>/sessions/memory_leaking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/memory_leaking/</guid><description>In this session we will learn how to track JavaScript memory leaks.
As web developers, we strive to build fast and robust web apps and servers. But, sometimes we unintentionally create memory leaks, which later on become a big issue that might even crash our app or server. In this session we will learn how to track JavaScript memory leaks.</description></item><item><title>Help! My Memory is Leaking</title><link>/speakers/gil_fink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/gil_fink/</guid><description>Gil Fink is a web development expert, Web Technologies GDE, Microsoft Development Technologies MVP and sparXys CEO. He is currently consulting for various enterprises and companies, where he helps to develop web based solutions. He is also co-author of several Microsoft Official Courses (MOCs) and training kits, co-author of &amp;ldquo;Pro Single Page Application Development&amp;rdquo; book (Apress), co-organizer of AngularUP and ReactNext conferences.
Website</description></item><item><title>Hero Talk from Google</title><link>/sessions/__hero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/__hero/</guid><description>Hero Talk</description></item><item><title>Istio, your kubernetes cluster best friend ❤️</title><link>/sessions/istio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/istio/</guid><description>In a distributed world, we are facing new challenges. Circuit-breaker, retry, timeout, blue-green deployment, A/B testing, pool-ejection&amp;hellip; replace our old monolith problem.
Istio is here to help us in those points, and even more!
In this presentation, we will see the tooling provided by Istio which can replace the Netflix stack and some dedicated frameworks in our micro-services environment. With this, we will see new paradigms of development brought by Istio to deploy and operate application with resiliency.</description></item><item><title>Istio, your kubernetes cluster best friend ❤️</title><link>/speakers/kevin_davin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/kevin_davin/</guid><description>A Google Developer Expert on Google Cloud and Gitlab Hero, I am above all passionate about tech, languages, infrastructure, and automation. Java, Kotlin, TypeScript are my day-to-day languages. I deploy all of those on the Google Kubernetes Engine with the GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Continuous Integration 🚀.
Addict of agility and DevOps, some of my missions were to help teams to follow those philosophies. From code quality analysis to unit or end-to-end tests setup all the way to continuous deployment and operation, I try to follow a project from birth to production.</description></item><item><title>Machine learning on the edge using TensorFlow Lite</title><link>/sessions/ml_using_tensorflow_lite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/ml_using_tensorflow_lite/</guid><description>What if you could perform machine learning on the edge, i.e on your mobile device? This would mean that you no longer would need the roundtrip to the server, no data will leave the device and you don&amp;rsquo;t even need an internet connection. In this session you will get an introduction to TensorFlow Lite so that you can use it in your own projects.
I will demonstrate how you can take a pre-trained model for image classification and convert it to TensorFlow Lite format.</description></item><item><title>Machine learning on the edge using TensorFlow Lite</title><link>/speakers/hakon_silfvernagel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/hakon_silfvernagel/</guid><description>Håkan holds a Master of Science degree in Electrical Engineering and in addition, he holds a Master’s degree in Leadership and Organizational behavior. He has also taken courses on university level in psychology, interaction design and human-computer interaction. He has 20 years’ experience of software development in various positions such as developer, tester, architect, project manager, scrum master, practice manager and team lead.
Håkan is Chairman of the local chapter of the Norwegian .</description></item><item><title>Making your Flutter Apps Secure</title><link>/sessions/make_flutter_secure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/make_flutter_secure/</guid><description>Security is one of the top concerns for Product Owners and higher management. This talk shows some cool ways you can look into as a developer to make your Flutter apps secure.
I will be sharing some tips for securing applications which include in-memory tokenization, using secure storages, some security rules for Firebase (maybe), securing the smaller app window, shared preferences, making secure https calls, hashing keys, obfuscation, etc.
Note: for this talk, attendees will need Flutter experience.</description></item><item><title>Making your Flutter apps secure</title><link>/speakers/waleed_arshad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/waleed_arshad/</guid><description>Waleed Arshad is a mobile technologist, a core developer, and one of the founders of Flutter Pakistan (a Flutter community in Pakistan). He has recently been titled as the first person from Pakistan to become a Google Developer Expert in Flutter. He mainly focuses on developing cross-platform mobile applications on Flutter and is always inclined towards consistently coming up with leading-edge technology orientations.
He has been a part of IBM, TPS Worldwide, Karachi Electric, Unikrew Solutions and is currently working in Karachi as a Senior Flutter Developer at VentureDive.</description></item><item><title>My Journey Of Building Robots</title><link>/sessions/robots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/robots/</guid><description>I am 14 years old and I have been coding and building robots since I was 9 years old. I have built 5 robots until now; ic4u and ic4u2- a robot guide dog for blind people, BB4All - a robot that is designed to help teachers and students and to prevent bullying. Hashmet the Android – the Android robot and DO the droid from Starwars.
In my session, I would like to talk about the technologies I have integrated into my robots such as Google Assistant API, Google Maps API, and Google AIY voice kit.</description></item><item><title>My Journey Of Building Robots</title><link>/speakers/selina_ornek/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/selina_ornek/</guid><description>My name is Selin Alara Örnek, I am 14 years old and I am currently a student in the 9th grade at Irmak High School, Istanbul. I started to learn to code when I was 9 years old and started building robots when I was 10. I speak English, Turkish, and French. I am learning C++ and Python through online courses and also whilst building my projects. When I get the chance I really enjoy attending events, talking about my projects, and receiving feedback from all different people.</description></item><item><title>Navigating the Flutter Ecosystem - Journey from Package Discovery to Publishing and Beyond</title><link>/sessions/flutter_ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/flutter_ecosystem/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Flutter is more than just an engine, a set of widgets, and some tools; it also includes a large ecosystem of packages to add functionality to your apps beyond what comes out of the box&amp;rdquo; - Chris Sells, Google Product Manager - Flutter.
Today, the Flutter ecosystem has more than 12,000 packages and new packages are being added to pub.dev everyday. As the Flutter package landscape is grows day by day, developers often find themselves searching endlessly for suitable packages and sometimes even end up reinventing the wheel.</description></item><item><title>Navigating the Flutter Ecosystem - Journey from Package Discovery to Publishing and Beyond</title><link>/speakers/ashita_prasad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/ashita_prasad/</guid><description>Ashita is a die-hard Flutterista and creator of Flutter Gems, a curated Flutter package guide which is available for free and trusted by more than 7000 Flutter developers across the globe.
Website</description></item><item><title>No way, JOSE!</title><link>/sessions/no_way_jose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/no_way_jose/</guid><description>Is your first thought when thinking about cryptography, “nope, that’s not for me!”? There’s no need to. When explained with simple examples, you can see the basics are not that complicated. The JavaScript Object Signing and Encryption, or JOSE for short is a framework that helps us deal with encryption. It describes ways to securely transfer data either signed (JWS) or encrypted (JWE). Let’s take a leap of faith and explore the wonderful world of cryptography together, shall we?</description></item><item><title>No way, JOSE!</title><link>/speakers/sam_bellen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/sam_bellen/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Google Developer Expert (GDE) who works as a developer evangelist at Auth0. At Auth0 we&amp;rsquo;re trying to make authentication and identification as easy as possible, while still keeping it secure.
After office hours, I like to play around with the web-audio API, and other &amp;ldquo;exotic&amp;rdquo; browser API&amp;rsquo;s. One of my side projects is a library to add audio effects to an audio input using JavaScript.
Website</description></item><item><title>Opening words</title><link>/sessions/__open/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/__open/</guid><description>Starting the conference day</description></item><item><title>Quiz</title><link>/sessions/__quiz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/__quiz/</guid><description>Short break</description></item><item><title>Short break</title><link>/sessions/__break/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/__break/</guid><description>Short break</description></item><item><title>Tales of a Mobile DevOps</title><link>/speakers/nicola_corti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/nicola_corti/</guid><description>Nicola Corti has been an Android Software Engineer since 2.2, and a Free and Open Source lover for as long as he remembers. He’s currently working as an Android Infrastructure Engineer at Spotify, building the audio experience for millions of Android users worldwide.
Nicola usually calls himself a ‘community addict’. He can’t survive without learning every day, sharing knowledge, and having fun with other developers. He’s also currently managing the GDG chapter in Stockholm and the one in Pisa.</description></item><item><title>Vue 3</title><link>/sessions/vue3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/vue3/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s look at what&amp;rsquo;s new in Vue.js 3!
Wait, you don&amp;rsquo;t know Vue? No problem, I will start the talk with a crash course on what Vue is and how to create websites with the framework.
Then I will talk about what changes have been made to Vue and the new Composition API.</description></item><item><title>Want more from your frontend framework! Re-thinking web dev experience</title><link>/speakers/jakub_holy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/jakub_holy/</guid><description>I’m a full stack Clojure(Script) developer coming originally from the JVM/JS land, coding professionally since 2005. During the years I have worked on projects large and small, long and short, local and international - and I have been scarred by too much legacy code. I care deeply about productivity (and thus Clojure and DevOps) and quality and enjoy sharing my discoveries on my blog. I come from the Czech Republic but live currently in Norway.</description></item></channel></rss>