<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Speakers on Devfest Norway 2020</title><link>/speakers/</link><description>Recent content in Speakers on Devfest Norway 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/speakers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CI/CD for Serverless Applications on CloudRun</title><link>/speakers/dharmesh_vaya/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/speakers/dharmesh_vaya/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Google Developer Expert (GDE) who works as a developer evangelist at Auth0. At Auth0 we&amp;rsquo;re trying to make authentication and identification as easy as possible, while still keeping it secure.
After office hours, I like to play around with the web-audio API, and other &amp;ldquo;exotic&amp;rdquo; browser API&amp;rsquo;s. One of my side projects is a library to add audio effects to an audio input using JavaScript.
Twitter</description></item><item><title>Help! My Memory is Leaking</title><link>/speakers/gil_fink/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/speakers/gil_fink/</guid><description>Gil Fink is a web development expert, Web Technologies GDE, Microsoft Development Technologies MVP and sparXys CEO. He is currently consulting for various enterprises and companies, where he helps to develop web based solutions. He is also co-author of several Microsoft Official Courses (MOCs) and training kits, co-author of &amp;ldquo;Pro Single Page Application Development&amp;rdquo; book (Apress), co-organizer of AngularUP and ReactNext conferences.
Website</description></item><item><title>Istio, your kubernetes cluster best friend ❤️</title><link>/speakers/kevin_davin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/speakers/kevin_davin/</guid><description>A Google Developer Expert on Google Cloud and Gitlab Hero, I am above all passionate about tech, languages, infrastructure, and automation. Java, Kotlin, TypeScript are my day-to-day languages. I deploy all of those on the Google Kubernetes Engine with the GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Continuous Integration 🚀.
Addict of agility and DevOps, some of my missions were to help teams to follow those philosophies. From code quality analysis to unit or end-to-end tests setup all the way to continuous deployment and operation, I try to follow a project from birth to production.</description></item><item><title>Want more from your frontend framework! Re-thinking web dev experience</title><link>/speakers/jakub_holy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/speakers/jakub_holy/</guid><description>I’m a full stack Clojure(Script) developer coming originally from the JVM/JS land, coding professionally since 2005. During the years I have worked on projects large and small, long and short, local and international - and I have been scarred by too much legacy code. I care deeply about productivity (and thus Clojure and DevOps) and quality and enjoy sharing my discoveries on my blog. I come from the Czech Republic but live currently in Norway.</description></item><item><title>Angular Material Design</title><link>/speakers/emma_twersky/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/emma_twersky/</guid><description>Emma is a Developer Advocate at Google. She is passionate about good user experiences and design.
I am new to the Google Angular team, and previously spoke about Android and accessibility. I am scheduled to speak at Dutch Angular, several other meetups, GDG UK + Ireland and ngChina in the upcoming month.
Twitter</description></item><item><title>Designing Fair Machine Learning Models</title><link>/speakers/sharmistha_chatterjee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/sharmistha_chatterjee/</guid><description>Sharmistha Chatterjee is a Data Science Evangelist with vast professional experience in the field of Machine Learning and Cloud applications. She has graduated from Aalto University (formerly Helsinki University of Technology). She has proven experience in both doing AI research and implementing scalable AI solutions for enterprises. She tries to bridge the gap between theory and practice.
She is an active blogger, speaker at different AI/ML conferences, Google Developer Expert in Machine Learning, and a Professional Cloud Architect.</description></item><item><title>My Journey Of Building Robots</title><link>/speakers/selina_ornek/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/selina_ornek/</guid><description>My name is Selin Alara Örnek, I am 14 years old and I am currently a student in the 9th grade at Irmak High School, Istanbul. I started to learn to code when I was 9 years old and started building robots when I was 10. I speak English, Turkish, and French. I am learning C++ and Python through online courses and also whilst building my projects. When I get the chance I really enjoy attending events, talking about my projects, and receiving feedback from all different people.</description></item><item><title>No way, JOSE!</title><link>/speakers/sam_bellen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/sam_bellen/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Google Developer Expert (GDE) who works as a developer evangelist at Auth0. At Auth0 we&amp;rsquo;re trying to make authentication and identification as easy as possible, while still keeping it secure.
After office hours, I like to play around with the web-audio API, and other &amp;ldquo;exotic&amp;rdquo; browser API&amp;rsquo;s. One of my side projects is a library to add audio effects to an audio input using JavaScript.
Website</description></item></channel></rss>