<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Speakers on Devfest Norway 2020</title><link>/speakers/</link><description>Recent content in Speakers on Devfest Norway 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/speakers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/speakers/gaute_meek_olsen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/gaute_meek_olsen/</guid><description>Gaute is a software developer from Norway. He always likes to learn new technology and create hobby projects from what he has learned. He mostly programmes in JavaScript, C#, Java and Kotlin.
Website Twitter GitHub</description></item><item><title/><link>/speakers/nivetha_maran/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/nivetha_maran/</guid><description>I am a Software Engineer with focus on frontend technologies on Angular, React, Javascript, etc, with industry experience of around 3 years. Besides my regular job, I am an ambassador for GDG/WTM Chennai community. More info can be found here https://gdg.community.dev/gdg-chennai/, where we conduct technical meetups, conferences, workshops to develop tech and soft skills for the local developer community. And a PROUD feminist.
Twitter</description></item><item><title>A Multiplatform triathlon -- Kotlin through Android, iOS and web</title><link>/speakers/carlos_mota/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/carlos_mota/</guid><description>Android tech lead at WIT Software, he can easily be spotted there working on the company RCS solution. Carlos is enthusiastic for new technology and always trying to reach those last 20% of all of his side projects that seem to be really far away. He loves to share his knowledge with others either by giving talks, teaching, writing or getting a cold beer in the nearest pub.
GDG Coimbra organizer and Kotlin evangelist, he also has a huge passion for travel, photography, space and the occasional run.</description></item><item><title>Angular Material Design</title><link>/speakers/emma_twersky/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/emma_twersky/</guid><description>Emma is a Developer Advocate at Google. She is passionate about good user experiences and design.
I am new to the Google Angular team, and previously spoke about Android and accessibility. I am scheduled to speak at Dutch Angular, several other meetups, GDG UK + Ireland and ngChina in the upcoming month.
Twitter</description></item><item><title>CI/CD for Serverless Applications on CloudRun</title><link>/speakers/dharmesh_vaya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/dharmesh_vaya/</guid><description>Dharmesh is a technologist known for his ability of developing enterprise applications on Cloud Platforms and fostering a spirit of innovation among teams, with a diverse experience around Banking, e-Commerce, Media/Entertainment to name a few. He is a Google Developer Expert for Google Cloud Platform/Payments and actively manages Google Cloud Developers Community, Mumbai.
Twitter</description></item><item><title>Designing Fair Machine Learning Models</title><link>/speakers/charmi_chokshi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/charmi_chokshi/</guid><description>Playing with data and predicting possibilities based on it is Charmi&amp;rsquo;s passion! From giving tech sessions at the local meetups to delivering tech-talks at global stages, she loves helping developers &amp;amp; students who look forward to growing their careers in the field of Artificial Intelligence.
She has worked in the pipeline of the Smart-cities Mission of India in the Deep Learning and Computer Vision domain at the Indian Space Research Organisation.</description></item><item><title>Designing Fair Machine Learning Models</title><link>/speakers/sharmistha_chatterjee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/sharmistha_chatterjee/</guid><description>Sharmistha Chatterjee is a Data Science Evangelist with vast professional experience in the field of Machine Learning and Cloud applications. She has graduated from Aalto University (formerly Helsinki University of Technology). She has proven experience in both doing AI research and implementing scalable AI solutions for enterprises. She tries to bridge the gap between theory and practice.
She is an active blogger, speaker at different AI/ML conferences, Google Developer Expert in Machine Learning, and a Professional Cloud Architect.</description></item><item><title>Famous App UIs Broken Down in Flutter Widgets</title><link>/speakers/sakina_abbas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/sakina_abbas/</guid><description>Being the Cofounder and CEO of ReacTree, a new-gen Software Development house, Sakina Abbas is all about solving problems through technology. She started off as a native Android developer and is now leading Flutter development and DevOps at ReacTree. To date, she has provided consultancies to numerous international and local clients and has built a number of custom solutions.
Website Twitter</description></item><item><title>Help! My Memory is Leaking</title><link>/speakers/gil_fink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/gil_fink/</guid><description>Gil Fink is a web development expert, Web Technologies GDE, Microsoft Development Technologies MVP and sparXys CEO. He is currently consulting for various enterprises and companies, where he helps to develop web based solutions. He is also co-author of several Microsoft Official Courses (MOCs) and training kits, co-author of &amp;ldquo;Pro Single Page Application Development&amp;rdquo; book (Apress), co-organizer of AngularUP and ReactNext conferences.
Website</description></item><item><title>Istio, your kubernetes cluster best friend ❤️</title><link>/speakers/kevin_davin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/kevin_davin/</guid><description>A Google Developer Expert on Google Cloud and Gitlab Hero, I am above all passionate about tech, languages, infrastructure, and automation. Java, Kotlin, TypeScript are my day-to-day languages. I deploy all of those on the Google Kubernetes Engine with the GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Continuous Integration 🚀.
Addict of agility and DevOps, some of my missions were to help teams to follow those philosophies. From code quality analysis to unit or end-to-end tests setup all the way to continuous deployment and operation, I try to follow a project from birth to production.</description></item><item><title>Machine learning on the edge using TensorFlow Lite</title><link>/speakers/hakon_silfvernagel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/hakon_silfvernagel/</guid><description>Håkan holds a Master of Science degree in Electrical Engineering and in addition, he holds a Master’s degree in Leadership and Organizational behavior. He has also taken courses on university level in psychology, interaction design and human-computer interaction. He has 20 years’ experience of software development in various positions such as developer, tester, architect, project manager, scrum master, practice manager and team lead.
Håkan is Chairman of the local chapter of the Norwegian .</description></item><item><title>Making your Flutter apps secure</title><link>/speakers/waleed_arshad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/waleed_arshad/</guid><description>Waleed Arshad is a mobile technologist, a core developer, and one of the founders of Flutter Pakistan (a Flutter community in Pakistan). He has recently been titled as the first person from Pakistan to become a Google Developer Expert in Flutter. He mainly focuses on developing cross-platform mobile applications on Flutter and is always inclined towards consistently coming up with leading-edge technology orientations.
He has been a part of IBM, TPS Worldwide, Karachi Electric, Unikrew Solutions and is currently working in Karachi as a Senior Flutter Developer at VentureDive.</description></item><item><title>My Journey Of Building Robots</title><link>/speakers/selin_ornek/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/selin_ornek/</guid><description>My name is Selin Alara Örnek, I am 14 years old and I am currently a student in the 9th grade at Irmak High School, Istanbul. I started to learn to code when I was 9 years old and started building robots when I was 10. I speak English, Turkish, and French. I am learning C++ and Python through online courses and also whilst building my projects. When I get the chance I really enjoy attending events, talking about my projects, and receiving feedback from all different people.</description></item><item><title>Navigating the Flutter Ecosystem - Journey from Package Discovery to Publishing and Beyond</title><link>/speakers/ashita_prasad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/ashita_prasad/</guid><description>Ashita is a die-hard Flutterista and creator of Flutter Gems, a curated Flutter package guide which is available for free and trusted by more than 7000 Flutter developers across the globe.
Website</description></item><item><title>No way, JOSE!</title><link>/speakers/sam_bellen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/sam_bellen/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Google Developer Expert (GDE) who works as a developer evangelist at Auth0. At Auth0 we&amp;rsquo;re trying to make authentication and identification as easy as possible, while still keeping it secure.
After office hours, I like to play around with the web-audio API, and other &amp;ldquo;exotic&amp;rdquo; browser API&amp;rsquo;s. One of my side projects is a library to add audio effects to an audio input using JavaScript.
Website</description></item><item><title>Tales of a Mobile DevOps</title><link>/speakers/nicola_corti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/nicola_corti/</guid><description>Nicola Corti has been an Android Software Engineer since 2.2, and a Free and Open Source lover for as long as he remembers. He’s currently working as an Android Infrastructure Engineer at Spotify, building the audio experience for millions of Android users worldwide.
Nicola usually calls himself a ‘community addict’. He can’t survive without learning every day, sharing knowledge, and having fun with other developers. He’s also currently managing the GDG chapter in Stockholm and the one in Pisa.</description></item><item><title>Want more from your frontend framework! Re-thinking web dev experience</title><link>/speakers/jakub_holy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/speakers/jakub_holy/</guid><description>I’m a full stack Clojure(Script) developer coming originally from the JVM/JS land, coding professionally since 2005. During the years I have worked on projects large and small, long and short, local and international - and I have been scarred by too much legacy code. I care deeply about productivity (and thus Clojure and DevOps) and quality and enjoy sharing my discoveries on my blog. I come from the Czech Republic but live currently in Norway.</description></item></channel></rss>