<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sessions on Devfest Norway 2020</title><link>/sessions/</link><description>Recent content in Sessions on Devfest Norway 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/sessions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tales of a Mobile DevOps</title><link>/sessions/mobile_devops/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/sessions/mobile_devops/</guid><description>There is a lot of material on developing mobile apps, but how about shipping it to the real world? In this session we will go through what is the role of a Mobile Infrastructure team and why is crucial to let your app reach your end users.
If you&amp;rsquo;re developing mobile apps, you probably know what&amp;rsquo;s one of your most important KPI: Store Rating.
In such an environment, speed is key.</description></item><item><title>Want more from your frontend framework! Re-thinking web dev experience</title><link>/sessions/want_more_from_your_frontend/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/sessions/want_more_from_your_frontend/</guid><description>Do you also love creating useful (web)apps and get easily frustrated by any friction in the development process? I will compare Redux + REST with a full-stack, component-centric solution based on a graph API (think GraphQL) that I came to love. You might not be able to use the same framework - Fulcro - but you can still look for similar, more developer-friendly solutions that implement some of the same ideas and provide some of the same functionality.</description></item><item><title>A Multiplatform triathlon -- Kotlin through Android, iOS and web</title><link>/sessions/multiplatform_triatholin_in_kotlin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/multiplatform_triatholin_in_kotlin/</guid><description>Do you ever had the dream that you could develop for one platform and you could easily reuse the code and create an app on another platform? Yup, there&amp;rsquo;s Kotlin Multiplatform 🙌
For several years now, we’ve been trying to find new solutions on how we could develop a single project and run it on all platforms. We’ve been seeing all types of solutions: some are web-based, others require you to learn a new language, and others even may require that you pay a monthly fee to use.</description></item><item><title>Angular Material Design</title><link>/sessions/angular_material_design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/angular_material_design/</guid><description>You may have heard of @angular/material, or added few in your project - but how can developers take advantage of Material to create cohesive applications? In this talk, we’ll learn how to leverage Angular and Material Design to create standard theming, custom design systems, and explore what’s next in Angular Material Design.
I will be covering @angular/material and Material Design within Angular. Since these are both Google products, the Google team has a unique vantage of understanding how we can better leverage Material Design within our applications moving forwards.</description></item><item><title>CI/CD for Serverless Applications on CloudRun</title><link>/sessions/serverless_on_cloudrun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/serverless_on_cloudrun/</guid><description>This is a hands-on demo of building a CI/CD pipeline for a web application deployed as a Serverless app using CloudRun.
Serverless application deployment is becoming quite popular and when it comes to GCP - CloudRun is the goto product/solution. This talk describes deploying a web application on CloudRun and how you can integrate your build pipelines using Cloud Build for the same. The talk would cover an end-to-end demo from building a docker container, pushing to GCR and then linking your repository to CloudBuild and ultimately deploying to CloudRun.</description></item><item><title>Closing words</title><link>/sessions/__close/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/__close/</guid><description>Closing words of the day</description></item><item><title>Designing Fair Machine Learning Models</title><link>/sessions/fair_ml_models/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/fair_ml_models/</guid><description>The talk illustrates different aspects of building fair models. It further exemplifies with different use-cases as to how different ML models (traditional and deep learning) can be built using different constraints and how we can choose the right KPI metrics to evaluate its fairness.
This talk will be co-presented with fellow ML GDE Charmi Chokshi.</description></item><item><title>Help! My Memory is Leaking</title><link>/sessions/memory_leaking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/memory_leaking/</guid><description>In this session we will learn how to track JavaScript memory leaks.
As web developers, we strive to build fast and robust web apps and servers. But, sometimes we unintentionally create memory leaks, which later on become a big issue that might even crash our app or server. In this session we will learn how to track JavaScript memory leaks.</description></item><item><title>Istio, your kubernetes cluster best friend ❤️</title><link>/sessions/istio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/istio/</guid><description>In a distributed world, we are facing new challenges. Circuit-breaker, retry, timeout, blue-green deployment, A/B testing, pool-ejection&amp;hellip; replace our old monolith problem.
Istio is here to help us in those points, and even more!
In this presentation, we will see the tooling provided by Istio which can replace the Netflix stack and some dedicated frameworks in our micro-services environment. With this, we will see new paradigms of development brought by Istio to deploy and operate application with resiliency.</description></item><item><title>Machine learning on the edge using TensorFlow Lite</title><link>/sessions/ml_using_tensorflow_lite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/ml_using_tensorflow_lite/</guid><description>What if you could perform machine learning on the edge, i.e on your mobile device? This would mean that you no longer would need the roundtrip to the server, no data will leave the device and you don&amp;rsquo;t even need an internet connection. In this session you will get an introduction to TensorFlow Lite so that you can use it in your own projects.
I will demonstrate how you can take a pre-trained model for image classification and convert it to TensorFlow Lite format.</description></item><item><title>Making your Flutter Apps Secure</title><link>/sessions/make_flutter_secure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/make_flutter_secure/</guid><description>Security is one of the top concerns for Product Owners and higher management. This talk shows some cool ways you can look into as a developer to make your Flutter apps secure.
I will be sharing some tips for securing applications which include in-memory tokenization, using secure storages, some security rules for Firebase (maybe), securing the smaller app window, shared preferences, making secure https calls, hashing keys, obfuscation, etc.
Note: for this talk, attendees will need Flutter experience.</description></item><item><title>My Journey Of Building Robots</title><link>/sessions/robots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/robots/</guid><description>I am 14 years old and I have been coding and building robots since I was 9 years old. I have built 5 robots until now; ic4u and ic4u2- a robot guide dog for blind people, BB4All - a robot that is designed to help teachers and students and to prevent bullying. Hashmet the Android – the Android robot and DO the droid from Starwars.
In my session, I would like to talk about the technologies I have integrated into my robots such as Google Assistant API, Google Maps API, and Google AIY voice kit.</description></item><item><title>Navigating the Flutter Ecosystem - Journey from Package Discovery to Publishing and Beyond</title><link>/sessions/flutter_ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/flutter_ecosystem/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Flutter is more than just an engine, a set of widgets, and some tools; it also includes a large ecosystem of packages to add functionality to your apps beyond what comes out of the box&amp;rdquo; - Chris Sells, Google Product Manager - Flutter.
Today, the Flutter ecosystem has more than 12,000 packages and new packages are being added to pub.dev everyday. As the Flutter package landscape is grows day by day, developers often find themselves searching endlessly for suitable packages and sometimes even end up reinventing the wheel.</description></item><item><title>No way, JOSE!</title><link>/sessions/no_way_jose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/no_way_jose/</guid><description>Is your first thought when thinking about cryptography, “nope, that’s not for me!”? There’s no need to. When explained with simple examples, you can see the basics are not that complicated. The JavaScript Object Signing and Encryption, or JOSE for short is a framework that helps us deal with encryption. It describes ways to securely transfer data either signed (JWS) or encrypted (JWE). Let’s take a leap of faith and explore the wonderful world of cryptography together, shall we?</description></item><item><title>Opening words</title><link>/sessions/__open/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/__open/</guid><description>Starting the conference day</description></item></channel></rss>