<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sessions on Devfest Norway 2020</title><link>/sessions/</link><description>Recent content in Sessions on Devfest Norway 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/sessions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Angular Material Design</title><link>/sessions/angular_material_design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/angular_material_design/</guid><description>You may have heard of @angular/material, or added few in your project - but how can developers take advantage of Material to create cohesive applications? In this talk, we’ll learn how to leverage Angular and Material Design to create standard theming, custom design systems, and explore what’s next in Angular Material Design.
I will be covering @angular/material and Material Design within Angular. Since these are both Google products, the Google team has a unique vantage of understanding how we can better leverage Material Design within our applications moving forwards.</description></item><item><title>Closing words</title><link>/sessions/__close/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/__close/</guid><description>Closing words of the day</description></item><item><title>Designing Fair Machine Learning Models</title><link>/sessions/fair_ml_models/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/fair_ml_models/</guid><description>The talk illustrates different aspects of building fair models. It further exemplifies with different use-cases as to how different ML models (traditional and deep learning) can be built using different constraints and how we can choose the right KPI metrics to evaluate its fairness.
This talk will be co-presented with fellow ML GDE Charmi Chokshi.</description></item><item><title>My Journey Of Building Robots</title><link>/sessions/robots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/robots/</guid><description>I am 14 years old and I have been coding and building robots since I was 9 years old. I have built 5 robots until now; ic4u and ic4u2- a robot guide dog for blind people, BB4All - a robot that is designed to help teachers and students and to prevent bullying. Hashmet the Android – the Android robot and DO the droid from Starwars.
In my session, I would like to talk about the technologies I have integrated into my robots such as Google Assistant API, Google Maps API, and Google AIY voice kit.</description></item><item><title>No way, JOSE!</title><link>/sessions/no_way_jose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/no_way_jose/</guid><description>Is your first thought when thinking about cryptography, “nope, that’s not for me!”? There’s no need to. When explained with simple examples, you can see the basics are not that complicated. The JavaScript Object Signing and Encryption, or JOSE for short is a framework that helps us deal with encryption. It describes ways to securely transfer data either signed (JWS) or encrypted (JWE). Let’s take a leap of faith and explore the wonderful world of cryptography together, shall we?</description></item><item><title>Opening words</title><link>/sessions/__open/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/__open/</guid><description>Starting the conference day</description></item></channel></rss>