<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>_backend on Devfest Norway 2020</title><link>/tags/_backend/</link><description>Recent content in _backend on Devfest Norway 2020</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/_backend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CI/CD for Serverless Applications on CloudRun</title><link>/sessions/serverless_on_cloudrun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/serverless_on_cloudrun/</guid><description>This is a hands-on demo of building a CI/CD pipeline for a web application deployed as a Serverless app using CloudRun.
Serverless application deployment is becoming quite popular and when it comes to GCP - CloudRun is the goto product/solution. This talk describes deploying a web application on CloudRun and how you can integrate your build pipelines using Cloud Build for the same. The talk would cover an end-to-end demo from building a docker container, pushing to GCR and then linking your repository to CloudBuild and ultimately deploying to CloudRun.</description></item><item><title>Help! My Memory is Leaking</title><link>/sessions/memory_leaking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/memory_leaking/</guid><description>In this session we will learn how to track JavaScript memory leaks.
As web developers, we strive to build fast and robust web apps and servers. But, sometimes we unintentionally create memory leaks, which later on become a big issue that might even crash our app or server. In this session we will learn how to track JavaScript memory leaks.</description></item><item><title>Istio, your kubernetes cluster best friend ❤️</title><link>/sessions/istio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/istio/</guid><description>In a distributed world, we are facing new challenges. Circuit-breaker, retry, timeout, blue-green deployment, A/B testing, pool-ejection&amp;hellip; replace our old monolith problem.
Istio is here to help us in those points, and even more!
In this presentation, we will see the tooling provided by Istio which can replace the Netflix stack and some dedicated frameworks in our micro-services environment. With this, we will see new paradigms of development brought by Istio to deploy and operate application with resiliency.</description></item><item><title>No way, JOSE!</title><link>/sessions/no_way_jose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sessions/no_way_jose/</guid><description>Is your first thought when thinking about cryptography, “nope, that’s not for me!”? There’s no need to. When explained with simple examples, you can see the basics are not that complicated. The JavaScript Object Signing and Encryption, or JOSE for short is a framework that helps us deal with encryption. It describes ways to securely transfer data either signed (JWS) or encrypted (JWE). Let’s take a leap of faith and explore the wonderful world of cryptography together, shall we?</description></item></channel></rss>